[Music]
[音乐]
本教程是关于如何制作一个
this tutorial is about how to make a
移动一块拉条，当你
拉它使垂直的一块幻灯片
this tutorial is about how to make a
moving piece a pull strip which when you
在整个页面上，我会告诉你我的
版本第一，这非常简单，
moving piece a pull strip which when you
pull it it makes a vertical piece slide
最基本的是，这里有V型折叠
当您拉开条带时，它就变成了一块
pull it it makes a vertical piece slide
across the page well I'll show you my
在页面上滑动，因此相当
有用的，那很简单
across the page well I'll show you my
version first which is quite simple and
机制我在书中得到的例子
这是Peter Rabbit弹出书吗
version first which is quite simple and
basic here it is you've got a v-fold and
而这个稍微多一点
拉动它时会使V型折叠复杂化
basic here it is you've got a v-fold and
as you pull the strip it makes a piece
该图是使用集线器清晰表达的
这里后面有一个枢纽，还有一个
as you pull the strip it makes a piece
glide across the page so it's quite
集线器所有者在运动件上
放下这个数字可以移动，所以我只是
glide across the page so it's quite
useful then it's quite a simple
会告诉你如何做这个
活动件和轮毂的说明
useful then it's quite a simple
mechanism the example I've got in books
教程27集线器和枢轴
您以这种方式看到的基础表
mechanism the example I've got in books
is this one the Peter Rabbit pop-up book
它有一个荡妇拉带要去
进入下面，然后移动
is this one the Peter Rabbit pop-up book
and this one is slightly more
首先要超越它
贴在V形折叠上，这是常规的V
and this one is slightly more
complicated the v-fold when you pull it
折这是教程二
对称正则直角V折
complicated the v-fold when you pull it
the figure is articulated its using hubs
将会向后折叠
页面关闭，我将其粘贴到
the figure is articulated its using hubs
there's a hub behind here and there's a
这一页
我已经放荡了
there's a hub behind here and there's a
hub owner on the moving piece so as you
在v形折叠前面
您可能想在后面做荡妇
hub owner on the moving piece so as you
put it the figure can move so I'm just
V形折叠，在这种情况下，您可能需要
这两个选项卡而不是前进
put it the figure can move so I'm just
going to show you how to make this
向后走，但我决定让他们走
从你身上倒退，就是这样
going to show you how to make this
moving piece and hubs are explained in
与我已经拥有的荡妇保持一致
切好的荡妇大约两毫米宽
moving piece and hubs are explained in
tutorial 27 hubs and pivots
然后我们可以关闭它关闭
页面，使其自然粘住
the base sheets that you see it that way
定位所有在
教程一，现在我们
the base sheets that you see it that way
it has a the pull strip is going to
在前面需要一块
将要移动的东西直立
it has a the pull strip is going to
go underneath and then the moving piece
所以也许我会把它放在
运动这将是运动
go underneath and then the moving piece
is going to come above it first we have
这将是拉力带
移动它，我将其粘贴到位
is going to come above it first we have
to stick on a v-fold this is a regular V
首先，在
运动图像贴在一端
to stick on a v-fold this is a regular V
fold this is tutorial number two a
拉条拉条总是使
他们的厚度翻倍了
fold this is tutorial number two a
symmetrical regular right angle V fold
中间给它额外的力量和
然后把胶水一路拉
symmetrical regular right angle V fold
there's going to fold down backwards as
那衬衫胶合上就好了
当你粘这些东西放他们
there's going to fold down backwards as
the page closes I'll just glue that to
弄平然后弄平
他们仍然可能会稍微弯曲
the page closes I'll just glue that to
the page
那就是现在我们可以将其倾斜
通过那里的插槽
I've made it with the is going to
页现在这实际上在这一点上
看起来好像很擅长
I've made it with the is going to
be in front of the v-fold
只是保持自己的直立
但是只是为了确保我们会再放一个
be in front of the v-fold
you might want to do the behind the
一块在前面，所以我放了一个小标签
一方面，然后另一端是
you might want to do the behind the
v-fold in which case you'd probably need
会紧密地融入其中
需要这么长，所以我要削减
v-fold in which case you'd probably need
these two tabs to go forwards instead of
关闭它，您可能想保留它为
长
these two tabs to go forwards instead of
backwards but I decided to make them go
另一侧的另一个滑动图像
在上面放一些胶水
backwards but I decided to make them go
backwards out of you so there it is it's
这些标签上的胶水要小心
如果时间太长，可能会妨碍您
backwards out of you so there it is it's
aligned with that that I've already
然后开始限制样式
动片，但我认为那是
aligned with that that I've already
cut is about two millimeters wide
好吧，现在如果我们拉这个，你可以看到
它很好地上下移动
cut is about two millimeters wide
then we can shut this down close the
您仍然需要另外一块
因此，使条带与
then we can shut this down close the
page so it finds its natural sticking
页面，所以我有一个很大的部分
这有点太大，所以
page so it finds its natural sticking
position all that's explained in
那样坚持下去，所以你只是
每个边缘需要一小滴胶水
position all that's explained in
tutorial one there's that now we're
要小心，但它不会丢失
在条带下并粘上所有东西
tutorial one there's that now we're
going to need a piece in front which is
所以只增加一点点
像涂在它的每一面
going to need a piece in front which is
going to hold the moving piece upright
很好，让我们看看是的，您可能想要
尽你所能
going to hold the moving piece upright
so maybe I'll put that on after the
要么切断它，要么你可以
剪掉它就这样剪掉
so maybe I'll put that on after the
movement this is going to be the moving
所以你可能想弯曲一点
在那里，您可以将其切断与
movement this is going to be the moving
piece this is going to be the pull strip
页面，并且仍然能够获取
握住它
piece this is going to be the pull strip
that moves it I'll glue this into place
有滑动的垂直图像
当然你可以把Suzy的
that moves it I'll glue this into place
first so a little bit of glue on the
一个在另一个后面，你可以
可能如果您足够聪明，可以
first so a little bit of glue on the
moving image stick that on one end of
把它们全部拉下来
但我需要你解决这个问题
moving image stick that on one end of
the pull strip pull strips always make
你自己
[音乐]
the pull strip pull strips always make
them double thickness it's scored down